<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE plist PUBLIC "-//Apple Computer//DTD PLIST 1.0//EN" "http://www.apple.com/DTDs/PropertyList-1.0.dtd">
<plist version="1.0">
  <dict>
    <key>nodeAttributes</key>
    <dict>
      <key>category</key>
      <string>Origami</string>
      <key>categories</key>
      <array>
        <string>Origami</string>
      </array>
      <key>description</key>
      <string>Lets you get clicks on Layer patches. It works with Render in Image patches, iterators, and the Phone patch. Here are its ports:

Down: Lets you know if the mouse is currently down on the layer. Useful for pressed states.
Click: Tells you when the layer is pressed and released. Use this to perform an action once the layer is clicked.
Tap: Tells you when the layer is tapped while the mouse is still. Useful for getting clicks on a scrollable layer.
Drag: Outputs a 1 if the user started dragging the layer and stays 1 until the mouse is released.
Enable: Lets you decide whether the layer should respond to interaction. One example of when you'd want to use this is if you had a shading layer in front of an interactive element. You'd need to disable interaction on the shading layer so you could get clicks on the layer behind it.


Origami 1.0
http://origami.facebook.com/
        
Use of this patch is subject to the license found at http://origami.facebook.com/license/
        
Copyright: (c) 2013, Facebook, Inc. All rights reserved.
        
Created by: Brandon Walkin</string>
      <key>name</key>
      <string>Interaction 2</string>
    </dict>
    <key>inputAttributes</key>
    <dict>
      <key>inputEnableInteraction</key>
      <dict>
        <key>description</key>
        <string>Enable interaction for this layer. Turn this off to have clicks pass through the layer.</string>
        <key>name</key>
        <string>Enable</string>
      </dict>
    </dict>
    <key>outputAttributes</key>
    <dict>
      <key>outputInteraction</key>
      <dict>
        <key>description</key>
        <string>Interaction</string>
        <key>name</key>
        <string>Interaction</string>
      </dict>
      <key>outputUp</key>
      <dict>
        <key>description</key>
        <string>Tells you when the layer is pressed and released. Use this to perform an action once the layer is clicked.</string>
        <key>name</key>
        <string>Click</string>
      </dict>
      <key>outputDrag</key>
      <dict>
        <key>description</key>
        <string>Outputs a 1 if the user started dragging the layer and stays 1 until the mouse is released.</string>
        <key>name</key>
        <string>Drag</string>
      </dict>
      <key>outputDown</key>
      <dict>
        <key>description</key>
        <string>Lets you know if the mouse is currently down on the layer. Useful for pressed states.</string>
        <key>name</key>
        <string>Down</string>
      </dict>
      <key>outputTap</key>
      <dict>
        <key>description</key>
        <string>Tells you when the layer is tapped while the mouse was still. Useful for getting clicks on a scrolling layer.</string>
        <key>name</key>
        <string>Tap</string>
      </dict>
    </dict>
  </dict>
</plist>